<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Social Link</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="al_hadeesa_telecom">Al Hadeesa Telecom</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="linkedin">linkedin</string>
    <string name="facebook">facebook</string>
    <string name="github">Github</string>
    <string name="helloword_gmail_com">helloword@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="facebook_account">Facebook Account</string>
    <string name="facebook_com_gmail_com">facebook.com@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="android_developer">Android Developer</string>
    <string name="android_developer_it_last_1_year">android developer it last 1 year .</string>
    <string name="muhammad_hadi">Muhammad Hadi</string>
    <string name="dec">Hello there! I\'m Muhammad hadi, an experienced Android developer passionate about creating innovative mobile applications that enhance user experiences.My GitHub repositories are a reflection of my dedication to building high-quality Android apps using the latest technologies and best practices. I strive to write clean, maintainable code and follow design patterns such as MVVM or MVP to ensure scalability and modularity.With a solid understanding of Java and Kotlin, I have developed a wide range of apps, including e-commerce platforms, social networking apps, and utility tools. I also have experience integrating third-party APIs, implementing Firebase services, and optimizing app performance. I believe in collaborative development and have experience working in agile teams, utilizing version control systems like Git to ensure seamless code collaboration and project management. Besides my practical experience, I keep myself updated with the latest trends and developments in the Android ecosystem by actively participating in online communities, attending tech conferences, and exploring open-source projects. .</string>
    <string-array name="Skills">
        <item>Native development</item>
        <item>Flutter</item>
        <item>Firebase Database</item>
        <item>API</item>
        <item>SQL</item>
        <item>Kotlin language</item>
        <item>Java language</item>
        <item>Dart language</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>